<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Allahabad Tourism</string>
    <string-array name="fragment_name">
        <item>Attraction</item>
        <item>Activity</item>
        <item>Shopping Center</item>
        <item>Industry</item>
        <item>Restaurant</item>
        <item>HelpLine</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Attractions-->
    <string-array name="attraction_name">
        <item>Anand Bhavan</item>
        <item>Allahabad Fort</item>
        <item>Alfred Park</item>
        <item>Allahabad Museum</item>
        <item>Fungaon Amusement</item>
        <item>Jawahar Lal Planetorium</item>
        <item>Patalpuri Temple</item>
        <item>Sangam Triveni</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="attraction_description_short">
        <item>Anand Bhavan is the ancestral home of Jawaharlal Nehru, the first Prime-Minister of India.</item>
        <item>Allahabad Fort is a fort built by the Mughal emperor Akbar at Allahabad, in 1583.</item>
        <item>Alfred Park is a public park in Allahabad. Built in 1870 to mark Prince Alfred\'s visit to the city</item>
        <item>The Allahabad Museum is a national-level museum in Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh.</item>
        <item>An amusement-cum-water park for all age groups so that the entire family can enjoy together</item>
        <item>It is situated beside Anand Bhavan the former residence of the Nehru-Gandhi family and now a museum.</item>
        <item>Built by the Mughal Emperor Akbar.</item>
        <item>Triveni Sangam in Allahabad is the confluence of three rivers, Yamuna, Ganga and the mythical Saraswati.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="attraction_description_long">
        <item>The Anand Bhavan is a historic house museum in Allahabad, India focusing on the Nehru Family. It was constructed by Indian political leader Motilal Nehru in the 1930s to serve as the residence of the Nehru family when the original mansion Swaraj Bhavan (previously called Anand Bhavan) was transformed into the local headquarters of the Indian National Congress.Anand Bhavan was donated to Indian government in 1970 by the then Prime Minister Indira Gandhi, the granddaughter of Motilal Nehru and daughter of Jawaharlal Nehru.</item>
        <item>Allahabad Fort (Hindi: इलाहाबाद क़िला, Urdu: الہ آباد قلعہ Ilāhābād Qila) is a fort built by the Mughal emperor Akbar at Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh, India in 1583. The fort stands on the banks of the Yamuna near its confluence with the river Ganges. It is recognised by the Archaeological Survey of India as a monument of national importance.</item>
        <item>Chandrasekhar Azad Park (British colonial era Alfred Park and informally Company Bagh) is a public park in Allahabad. Built in 1870 to mark Prince Alfred  visit to the city, with an area of 133 acres, it is the biggest park in Allahabad. It was renamed after freedom fighter Chandra Shekhar Azad, who sacrificed his life here, during the Indian independence struggle in 1931. Originally and still famously the park is known as Alfred Park.</item>
        <item>The Allahabad Museum is a national-level museum in Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh. Established in 1931, it is known for its rich collection and unique objects of art, and is funded by Ministry of Culture. Moreover, it is a premier research centre for archaeologists, historians and academicians and carries out extensive research activities and publications in archaeology, art and literature. Its rock art gallery has the largest collection of prehistoric paintings displayed in India dating from 14,000 B.C to 2000 B.C. The museum, using solar power system, has become the first museum in the country to become self-reliant in power generation.</item>
        <item>As the name suggests, Fun Gaon Water Park in Allahabad is a fun-filled place to be in. Literally meaning “A village of Fun” – Fun Gaon is situated on Kaushambi Road in Allahabad. It is a popular water, amusement park of Allahabad and is a fun place for people of all age groups. So, it has something to offer for every visitor. The water at this park is quite clean, and thus the quality and cleanliness attracts huge number of visitors.</item>
        <item>The Jawahar Planetarium is located in the city of Allahabad in Uttar Pradesh, India. It was built in 1979 and is situated beside Anand Bhavan the former residence of the Nehru-Gandhi family and now a museum. It is managed by the Jawaharlal Nehru Memorial Fund (estb. 1964), which has its headquarters at Teen Murti House, New Delhi. Each year, the prestigious Jawaharlal Nehru Memorial Lecture is also held at the planetarium, organised under the auspices of Jawaharlal Nehru Memorial Fund on the birth anniversary of Indias first prime minister, November 14.</item>
        <item>"Within this underground temple, inside the fort, lies the Akshaya Vat - or the immortal tree."Believed to have been visited by Lord Rama, the temple was also seen by the famous Chinese traveler and writer Hiuen Tsang during his visit to this place.</item>
        <item>In Hindu tradition Triveni Sangam is the "confluence" of three rivers. Sangama is the Sanskrit word for confluence. The point of confluence is a sacred place for Hindus. A bath here is said to flush away all of ones sins and free one from the cycle of rebirth.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="attractions_where">
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/hLDB9sSmRLU2</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/ivD9j55e8sG2</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/2Pa8rHMMery</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/spXza8yoEpA2</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/sB1Dq7HrWAn</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/8FWkjoV382T2</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/pdS7TDjPbB42</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/FenkQX97bSy</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Activities-->
    <string-array name="activities_name">
        <item>Para Motoring</item>
        <item>Go Karting</item>
        <item>Segway Tour</item>
        <item>Camping</item>
        <item>Gaming Vegas</item>
        <item>Ice Skating</item>
        <item>Trekking</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="activities_short_desc">
        <item>Enjoy a session of paramotoring which lets you fly in the sky like a bird with the help of a paramotor</item>
        <item>5-storey victory tower with balconies</item>
        <item>Palatial 16th-century tomb of Humayun</item>
        <item>1920s triumphal arch and war memorial</item>
        <item>Vast, 17th-century Mughal-style mosque</item>
        <item>Temple with a flower-like design</item>
        <item>18th-century astronomy complex</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="what">What?</string>
    <string name="when">When?</string>
    <string name="where">Where?</string>
    <string name="maps">Open in maps</string>
    <string name="how_much">How Much?</string>
    <string-array name="activities_what">
        <item>
            &#8226; Enjoy a session of paramotoring which lets you fly in the sky like a bird with the help of a paramotor.\n
            &#8226; Get magnificent views of the surroundings from a height as you get clicked by a professional.\n
            &#8226; You can also enjoy other activities like Burma Bridge and Pool Table along with cake cutting
        </item>
        <item>
            &#8226; A pool table is also present in the premises.\n
            &#8226; All participants are given a 5 minute briefing before entering the circuit.\n
            &#8226; Free wi-fi.\n
            &#8226; One-of-a-kind indoor circuit.\n
            &#8226; Shoe racks and lockers are available for the customers.\n
            &#8226; Sky Karting offers a world-class racing track by a Spain and Germany based firm Protex Karting.\n
            &#8226; The go-karting circuit has a brew-pub right below it.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            &#8226; A unique mode of exploring historic buildings, monuments and memorials.\n
            &#8226; Safety gear and trained instructors.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            &#8226; Enjoy a fun-filled camping session with various games and activities for 8 hours in Allahabad.\n
            &#8226; The camp is ideal for those who want to spend a delightful time with a group of friends or family.\n
            &#8226; This 8 hour camp also includes lunch and evening tea with snacks.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            &#8226; Bowling Shoes and Socks are compulsory on the lanes. Shoe Rental: Rs.30/Per Game, Socks: Rs.40 to be paid directly to the merchant.\n
            &#8226; Play the game of bowling in a UV light experience.\n
            &#8226; Play the game on amazing UV lit Michael Jackson, Marilyn Monroe, Elvis Presley and Evil Knievel bowling lanes.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            &#8226; GA safety guidelines and training session takes place before each round of skating.\n
            &#8226; A souvenir shop for photographs, T-shirts, etc. is available.\n
            &#8226; Children are provided warm clothing if they feel too cold.\n
            &#8226; Lockers and changing room facilities are available.\n
            &#8226; Professional guides are available at all times.\n
            &#8226; Professional medical assistance is available at all times.\n
            &#8226; Socks are on sale in case one feels too cold.\n
            &#8226; The key attractions are a natural ice rink, an in-house DJ, sound and light audio systems.\n
            &#8226; There is a fully operational bar and food station available.\n
            &#8226; iSKATE is Indias first natural ice skating rink and café.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            &#8226; Enjoy the scenic beauty of the place while doing this activity.\n
            &#8226; Enjoy this adventure with your family and friends along with a expert guide.\n
            &#8226; Relax after a tiring day in the tents provided by the company.\n
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activities_when">
        <item>All Days, From 05:30AM</item>
        <item>Monday to Friday, 12:00PM to 11:00PM</item>
        <item>All Days, From 05:15AM</item>
        <item>All Days, From 10:00AM</item>
        <item>All Days, 11:00AM to 09:00PM</item>
        <item>Monday to Friday, 10:00AM to 09:00PM</item>
        <item>All Days, From 07:00AM</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="activities_how_much">
        <item>Couple : ₹8999</item>
        <item>Adult and Child : ₹415</item>
        <item>Adult and Child : ₹2000</item>
        <item>Adult : ₹930, Child : ₹650</item>
        <item>Adult and Child : ₹299</item>
        <item>Adult and Child : ₹499</item>
        <item>Adult and Child : ₹1199</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- Using as array so that it can be populaated as per the need -->
    <string-array name="activities_where">
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/R3fXs7RnAvx</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="shopping_name">
        <item>P Square Mall</item>
        <item>Vinyak City</item>
        <item>Sasta Mart</item>
        <item>Shree Sai IMC</item>
        <item>Global Sky Shop</item>
        <item>Prayag Pet world</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="shopping_short_desc">
        <item>218 E/71, MG Marg, Civil Lines, Madhopur, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211001</item>
        <item>48/24, Sardar Patel Marg, Civil Lines, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211001</item>
        <item>85 D Daud Nagar Naini, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211008</item>
        <item>41F/70A/5B/1 MADHOPUR PATTI UP, Kharkauni, Naini, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211008</item>
        <item>05 allahabad, A. D. A. Colony, Naini, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211008</item>
        <item>38/1, Near Jeetlal Chauraha, P.A.C. Colony, Naini, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211008</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="shopping_description_long">
        <item>A quiet good mall with free parking. Shopping options and a quick are easily available here. There are several fast food chains and restaurants to go to. Other franchise here includes Amway etc.</item>
        <item>The best mall and shopping complex in the city. Almost every famous brand is available here. The gaming console is good with number of gaming options available. Restaurants are a bit expensive.</item>
        <item>Not the best mall or shopping complex in the city.But, Almost every famous brand is available here. The gaming console is good with number of gaming options available. Restaurants are a bit expensive.</item>
        <item>Trader and distributor of teleshopping products, plastic products, buckets, plastic tiffin, plastic lunch box, plastic mug, plastic spoon, plastic</item>
        <item>Global Sky Shop - Ecommerce Shop / Online Business of zipper top, mayra womens polyester 34 sleeve top and gear black and blue casual backpack ba in Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh.</item>
        <item>Pet Training Service, German Shepherd Pet Dog and Pet Dog Food Wholesaler offered by Prayag Dog Kennel from Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh, India.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="shopping_where">
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/tGhj1dAgVRo</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/AB6KSKy9nR22</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/v1qNiV8G9AQ2</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/tDVG6FuUFQE2</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/YmhaFwxCfpT2</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/ji23KmrDLU62</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="industry_name">
        <item>Techno Industries</item>
        <item>myBPC</item>
        <item>EMC Limited</item>
        <item>Reliance</item>
        <item>Alstom</item>
        <item>SAIL INDIA</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="industry_short_desc">
        <item> 67/23/41- J, Ramanand Nagar, Allahpur, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211006</item>
        <item>Mirzapur Road, Naini, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211009</item>
        <item>Naini Railway, Mirzapur Rd, Naini, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211010</item>
        <item>154, Tilak Nagar, Allahpur, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211006</item>
        <item>Naini, Mirzapur Rd, Naini, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211010</item>
        <item>Cheoiki, Mirzapur Rd, Naini, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211010</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Using array so that it can be populated as needed -->
    <string-array name="industry_description_long">
        <item>They as a full service mechanical product developer and manufacturer, offer a wide range of quality product development. This includes manufacturing Telecom connectors, BTS Subrack Front Plates and various fasteners for assembly and installations.</item>
        <item>They as a full service mechanical product developer and manufacturer, offer a wide range of quality product development. This includes manufacturing Telecom connectors, BTS Subrack Front Plates and various fasteners for assembly and installations.</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Using array so that it can be populated as needed -->
    <string-array name="industry_where">
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/hLDB9sSmRLU2</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/hLDB9sSmRLU2</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="restaurant_name">
        <item>KFC</item>
        <item>Eat On</item>
        <item>McDonalds</item>
        <item>Subway</item>
        <item>PizzaHut</item>
        <item>Dominos</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="restaurant_short_desc">
        <item>218 E/71, MG Marg, Civil Lines, Madhopur, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211001</item>
        <item>48/24, Sardar Patel Marg, Civil Lines, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211001</item>
        <item>85 D Daud Nagar Naini, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211008</item>
        <item>41F/70A/5B/1 MADHOPUR PATTI UP, Kharkauni, Naini, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211008</item>
        <item>05 allahabad, A. D. A. Colony, Naini, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211008</item>
        <item>38/1, Near Jeetlal Chauraha, P.A.C. Colony, Naini, Allahabad, Uttar Pradesh 211008</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Using array so that it can be populated as needed -->
    <string-array name="restaurant_description_long">
        <item>A quiet good restaurant in the city. Cards are accepted here and a pre order are easily available here. There are several fast food chains to have here.</item>
        <item>A quiet good restaurant in the city. Cards are accepted here and a pre order are easily available here. There are several fast food chains to have here.</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Using array so that it can be populated as needed -->
    <string-array name="restaurant_where">
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/hLDB9sSmRLU2</item>
        <item>https://goo.gl/maps/hLDB9sSmRLU2</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string-array name="helpline_position">
        <item>Tourist Officer</item>
        <item>District Magistrate</item>
        <item>S.P.</item>
        <item>Army Officer</item>
        <item>D.S.P</item>
        <item>Govt. Hospital</item>
        <item>Ambulance</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="helpline_mobile">
        <item>94XXX5XXX1</item>
        <item>94X4XXXXX2</item>
        <item>93XXXXXXX1</item>
        <item>93XXX3XXX2</item>
        <item>97XX2XXXX5</item>
        <item>94XXXX25X1</item>
        <item>94X67XXXX1</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
